Guide to the UE News Photograph Collection, 1933-1998 UE.14.1
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Districts and Locals, 1940-1998; 14.1.2.
  - Local 454: North American Phillips, Dobbs Ferry, NJ (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Local 455: General Electric, Trenton (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Local 456: Westinghouse Elevator, Jersey City (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Local 475: Sklar Manufacturing, Brooklyn (Box 11, Folder 55-56)
  - Local 475: Sklar Manufacturing, Strike Photographs, Brooklyn (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Local 477: Federal Telephone and Radio (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Local 1202: Taglibue, Brooklyn (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Local 1206: New York City (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Local 1217: Fairchild Aerial, New York City (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Local 1225: Brooklyn (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Local 1227: Morey Machinery, Conmar, Newark and New York (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Local 1237: Remington Rand, New York City (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - District 4: Vacation Camp (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - District 4: General (Box 12, Folder 08-12)
  - Local 504: Westinghouse, Hamilton (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Local 505 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Local 507 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Local 510 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Local 512: A.C. Wickman Ltd., Toronto (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Local 514: Penn Controls, Scarborough, Ontario (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Local 517: Provincial Gas, Welland (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Local 520: Hamilton (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Local 521: Canada Wire and Cable (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Local 523: Welland, Ontario (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Local 524: General Electric, Peterborough (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Local 531: Northern Electric, Bramela, Ontario (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Local 531: RCA, Peterborough (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Local 539: GE Tube and Electronics, Toronto (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Local 543: Lanark Mfg. Co., Welland, Ontario (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Local 545: Black and Decker (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Local 558: WABCO (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - District 5: General (Box 13, Folder 18-21)
  - Local 502 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Local 506: Labor Day Celebration, 1944 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Local 506: Veterans Lobbying Harrisburg, 1946 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Local 506: U.E.R.M.A. Meeting, 1946 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Local 506: Joint Stewards Meeting on Friday, July 29, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Local 506 Gives Aid to Miners, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Local 506: Two-Dollar Increase Demonstration, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Local 506: Crowd at Demonstration and Contract Ratification, 1949-1950 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Local 506 Goes to Washington, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Local 506: National Labor Relations Board Vote, December 1954 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Local 506: Pensioners Meeting, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Local 506: Petition Signing Polaroid from UE News, May 12, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Local 506: Individual Member Photographs in UE News, September 1, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Local 506 UE helps IUE Local 613 Erie Resister Workers on Strike (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Local 506: UE Convention in Chicago (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Local 506: Installation of New Officers (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Local 506: Photos from UE News, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Local 506: Retirees Photos by Custom Photography Graphic Arts Photo Service in UE News, June 3, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Local 506: Retirees Picnic Photos in UE News, July 26, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Local 506: District 6 Council Meeting in Erie, PA (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Local 506: UE Convention Photos- UE Conventions 27th -34th, 1960s (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Local 506: Strike, Meetings, and Demonstrations, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Local 506: Strike and Settlement, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Local 506: Supports Grape Boycott (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Local 506: UE Convention Photos- UE Conventions 35th -44th, 1970s (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Local 506: Photos from UE News, April 6, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Local 506: Peace March in Washington (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Local 506: Photographs from UE News, April 30, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Local 506: GE Negotiations, April 16, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Local 506: GE Negotiations, May 14, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Local 506: GE Contract Ratification Meeting, June 25, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Local 506: Erie City Council and Local 506 Protest Rising Gas Rates, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Local 506 Wins Back Pay, May 1977 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Local 506: New Member Installation, July 1977 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Local 506: Retirees Meeting, April 1948 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Local 506 Protest Natural Gas Prices, April 21, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Local 506: Winning Back Pay (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Local 506 Individual Member Photographs, March 22, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Local 506 Fights Plant Closing, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Local 506: Fighting Job Loss, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Local 506, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Local 506, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Local 506: Congressman Robert Edgar, April 1986 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Local 506: Protests and Negotiations, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Local 506: Stewards Conference, November 1, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Local 506: City Council Meeting, December 22, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Local 506: Miscellaneous Photographs, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Local 506: Steward's Conference In UE News, November 1, 1986 and January 12, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Local 506: Fights Job Loss, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Local 506: Job Loss Demonstrations (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Local 506: 50th Anniversary, May 18, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Local 506: Activities, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Local 506: Steward's Conference Color Photos, January 30, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Local 506: East Gate Rally Color Photos, May 17, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Local 506: Miscellaneous, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Local 506, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Local 506: Convention Photos, 1980s (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Local 506: Stewards (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - Local 506: Executive Board (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Local 506: Union Hall (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Local 506: Social Life (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - Local 506: Individual File: Adams, Dallas (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - Local 506: Individual File: Borgia, Joseph (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Local 506: Individual File: Britton, Harry (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - Local 506: Individual File: Brown, Thomas (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - Local 506: Individual File: Burns, Fred (Box 14, Folder 66)
  - Local 506: Individual File: Calabrese, Joseph (Box 14, Folder 67)
  - Local 506: Individual File: Cooney, Bud (Box 14, Folder 68)
  - Local 506: Individual File: Fioravanti, Adam (Box 14, Folder 69)
  - Local 506: Individual File: Kennedy, James (Box 14, Folder 70)
  - Local 506: Individual File: Kester, David (Box 14, Folder 71)
  - Local 506: Individual File: Lecorchick, Raymond (Box 14, Folder 72)
  - Local 506: Individual File: Mancini, John (Box 14, Folder 73)
  - Local 506: Individual File: McCollough, Art (Box 14, Folder 74)
  - Local 506: Individual File: Nelson, James (Box 14, Folder 75)
  - Local 506: Individual File: Nelson, John (Box 14, Folder 76)
  - Local 506: Individual File: Savelli, John (Box 14, Folder 77)
  - Local 506: Individual File: Wagner, Judy (Box 14, Folder 78)
  - Local 506: Individual File: Wassell, John (Box 14, Folder 79)
  - Local 506: Individual File: Thumbnails (Box 14, Folder 80)
  - Local 506: Miscellaneous Group Meetings (Box 14, Folder 81)
  - Local 506: Meeting (Box 14, Folder 82)
  - Local 506: Membership Banner (Box 14, Folder 83)
  - Local 506: Miscellaneous Photos (Box 14, Folder 84)
  - Local 506: Labor Legacy Photocopies (Box 14, Folder 85)
  - Local 601: Voter Registration and Executive Board (Box 14, Folder 86)
  - Local 601: Workers Pledge Full War Production (Box 14, Folder 87)
  - Local 601: Westinghouse Demonstration Parade (Box 14, Folder 88)
  - Local 601: Strike Photographs (Box 14, Folder 89)
  - Local 601: Kid's Parade in East Pittsburgh, March 1946 (Box 14, Folder 90)
  - Local 601: Equal Pay Demonstration (Box 14, Folder 91)
  - Local 601: Strike Agreement, 1946 (Box 14, Folder 92)
  - Local 601: Stoppage Rally, July 1946 (Box 14, Folder 93)
  - Local 601: OPA Petition Signing, July 6, 1946 (Box 14, Folder 94)
  - Local 601: Organizing Veterans Program (Box 14, Folder 95)
  - Local 601: Veto Taft-Hartley Petition Signing, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 96)
  - Local 601: One-Day Work Stoppage, May 1947 (Box 14, Folder 97)
  - Local 601: Henry Wallace Campaign, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 98)
  - Local 601: Demonstration in Turtle Creek Stadium (Box 14, Folder 99)
  - Local 601: UE versus IUE, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 100)
  - Local 601: House on Un-American Activities Committee, August 22, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 101)
  - Local 601: James Matles and Philip Murray visit East Pittsburgh, November 1949 (Box 14, Folder 102)
  - Local 601: Executive Board, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 103)
  - Local 601: Philip Murray and IUE Parade (Box 14, Folder 104)
  - Local 601: Defending the UE Meeting, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 105)
  - Local 601: Matthew Cvetic at East Pittsburgh High School (Box 14, Folder 106)
  - Local 601: East Pittsburgh Westinghouse NLRB Election Petition, May 28, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 107)
  - Local 601: Settles Grievances, November 1951 (Box 14, Folder 108)
  - Local 601: Mass Meeting, March 31, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 109)
  - Local 601: Pamphlet Distribution, April 14, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 110)
  - Local 601: Nuttall Workers Vote to Strike (Box 14, Folder 111)
  - Local 601: Nuttall Strike, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 112)
  - Local 601: Nuttall Workers Collect Donation, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 113)
  - Local 601: Office Break, September 1, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 114)
  - Local 601: Union Hall (Box 14, Folder 115)
  - Local 601: Stewards (Box 14, Folder 116)
  - Local 601: Member Thumbnails (Box 14, Folder 117)
  - Local 601: Individual Portraits with Thumbnails (Box 14, Folder 118)
  - Local 601: Nuttall Workers In UE News, September 15, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 119)
  - Local 601: Nuttall Workers In UE News, July 21, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 120)
  - Local 601: Individual Portraits: A (Box 14, Folder 121)
  - Local 601: Individual Portraits: B (Box 14, Folder 122)
  - Local 601: Individual Portraits: C (Box 14, Folder 123)
  - Local 601: Individual Portraits: D (Box 14, Folder 124)
  - Local 601: Individual File: Angelo, Anthony (Box 14, Folder 125)
  - Local 601: Individual File: Beveridge, Campbell "Scotty" (Box 14, Folder 126)
  - Local 601: Individual File: Bolyer, Carl (Box 14, Folder 127)
  - Local 601: Individual File: Byers, B.D. "Red" (Box 14, Folder 128)
  - Local 601: Individual File: Darin, Margaret (Box 14, Folder 129)
  - Local 601: Individual File: Emspak, Julius (Box 14, Folder 130)
  - Local 601: Individual File: Fitzgerald, Albert (Box 14, Folder 131)
  - Local 601: Individual File: Fitzpatrick, Michael (Box 14, Folder 132)
  - Local 601: Individual File: Fitzpatrick, James "Tommie" (Box 14, Folder 133)
  - Local 601: Individual File: Fitzpatrick, Thomas J. (Box 14, Folder 134)
  - Local 601: Individual File: Gibbs, George (Box 14, Folder 135)
  - Local 601: Individual File: Goodman, Sampson (Box 14, Folder 136)
  - Local 601: Individual File: Harper, William (Box 14, Folder 137)
  - Local 601: Individual File: Kirkwood, Robert (Box 14, Folder 138)
  - Local 601: Individual File: Matles, James (Box 14, Folder 139)
  - Local 601: Individual File: Mechling, Porter (Box 14, Folder 140)
  - Local 601: Individual File: Murray, Philip (Box 14, Folder 141)
  - Local 601: Individual File: Oyler, Al (Box 14, Folder 142)
  - Local 601: Individual File: Piazza, Ella (Box 14, Folder 143)
  - Local 601: Individual File: Whisner, Robert (Box 14, Folder 144)
  - Local 601: At Work (Box 14, Folder 145)
  - Local 601: Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 14, Folder 146)
  - Local 601: Miscellaneous Individuals (Box 14, Folder 147)
  - Local 601: Miscellaneous (Box 14, Folder 148)
  - Local 601: Miscellaneous Color Photos (Box 14, Folder 149)
  - Local 602: General Electric (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Local 603: Windsor Electric (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Local 605: Cameron (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Local 606: Percalier Manufacturing (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Local 608: Duquesne Light (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Local 610: USO Hayride (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Local 610: FDR campaign (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Local 610: Veterans, 1946 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Local 610: Air Brake Day Shift Mass Meeting, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Local 610: Pensioners, December 1950s (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Local 610: Pension and Insurance Negotiations (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Local 610: Assisting Striking United Mine Workers, March 6, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Local 610: UE versus IUE, June 26, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Local 610: Lobbying in Harrisburg (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Local 610: Collections for Strikers (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Local 610: Petition Signing, May 12, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Local 610: Members In UE News, June 21, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Local 610: Annual Picnic, August 17, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Local 610: Supporting Striking Steelworkers (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Local 610: Annual Picnic, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Local 610: Christmas Food Drives (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Local 610: Annual Picnic, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Local 610: Prospective Pensioners (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Local 610: Annual Picnic, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Local 610, July 24, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Local 610: Strike, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Local 610: Contract Vote, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Local 610, November 1969 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Local 610: Contract Acceptance Vote, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Local 610: Collecting Refunds, April 20, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Local 610: Retirees, 1970s (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Local 610: Officers Initiation (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Local 610: Steward Council (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Local 610: Retirees Demonstration, August 26, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Local 610: Vaccination Clinic, March 24, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Local 610: Meeting, August 1975 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Local 610: WABCO (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Local 610, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Local 610: Meeting, June 2, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Local 610: Washington Delegation, May 11, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Local 610: Joint WABCO 610 and Canadian Meeting, August 10, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Local 610: WABCO Strike, November 1981 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Local 610: Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Local 610: Strike, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Local 610: Concert with Peter Seeger, March 1982 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Local 610: Fight for Jobs, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Local 610, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Local 610, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Local 610: New York City Rally, October 28, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Local 610, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Local 610: Swissvale Public Hearing, April 27, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Local 610, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Local 610, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Local 610, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Local 610: Annual Scholarship Awards (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Local 610: Social Life (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Local 610: WABCO Plant (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Local 610: Individual File: Bobich, George (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Local 610: Individual File: Brush, Charles (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Local 610: Individual File: Carbo, Michael (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Local 610: Individual File: Holt, Arthur (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Local 610: Individual File: Huot, Edward (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Local 610: Individual File: Jones, Alice (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Local 610: Individual File: Robinson, Walter (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - Local 610: Miscellaneous Group Photographs (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - Local 610: Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - Local 610: Miscellaneous Individuals (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - Local 611: Sylvania Plant (Box 15, Folder 68)
  - Local 612: Day of Demonstration (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - Local 612: UE News Photos, 1954-1979 (Box 15, Folder 70)
  - Local 612: Union Members, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 71)
  - Local 612, 1979, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - Local 612: Union Members, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - Local 612: Grocery Distribution (Box 15, Folder 74)
  - Local 612: Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 75)
  - Local 612: Paul J. Clark Sr. (Box 15, Folder 76)
  - Local 612: Paul J. Clark Jr. (Box 15, Folder 77)
  - Local 613: Allis-Chalmers Plant (Box 15, Folder 78)
  - Local 614: Williamsport Battery Plant (Box 15, Folder 79)
  - Local 615: Pennsylvania Electric Coil Company (Box 15, Folder 80)
  - Local 616: Janecki Manufacturing (Box 15, Folder 81)
  - Local 617: Sharon Westinghouse (Box 15, Folder 82)
  - Local 618: Miscellaneous Members, 1950s (Box 15, Folder 83)
  - Local 618: Frank and Roy Christoph (Box 15, Folder 84)
  - Local 618: Members (Box 15, Folder 85)
  - Local 618: Strike Photos, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 86)
  - Local 618: Members, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 87)
  - Local 619: Westinghouse Service (Box 15, Folder 88)
  - Local 621: American Meter (Box 15, Folder 89)
  - Local 622: Stupakoff Ceramics and Carborundum Company (Box 15, Folder 90)
  - Local 623: Hanlon and Wilson Vote for Union Representation (Box 15, Folder 91)
  - Local 623: Members in UE News, July 21, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 92)
  - Local 623: Negotiating for Wage Increase (Box 15, Folder 93)
  - Local 623: Hanlon and Wilson Strike (Box 15, Folder 94)
  - Local 623: Organizing WIMCO Metal (Box 15, Folder 95)
  - Local 623: Strike at Woodroe (Box 15, Folder 96)
  - Local 623: Meeting with Pennsylvania Commercial Heat Treating, August 26, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 97)
  - Local 623: LIMPCO Strike (Box 15, Folder 98)
  - Local 623: Signing Three-Year Contract (Box 15, Folder 99)
  - Local 623: Strike, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 100)
  - Local 623: Meeting with Congressmen Scanlon and Wright (Box 15, Folder 101)
  - Local 623: Individual File: Coyle, William (Box 15, Folder 102)
  - Local 623: Miscellaneous Early Local Photographs (Box 15, Folder 103)
  - Local 623: Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 15, Folder 104)
  - Local 624: Robinson Manufacturing (Box 15, Folder 105)
  - Local 625: ITE Circuit Breaker (Box 15, Folder 106)
  - Local 626: Standard Sanitary (Box 15, Folder 107)
  - Local 627: Westinghouse, Fairmont, WV (Box 15, Folder 108)
  - Local 628: Darling Valve, Williamsport (Box 15, Folder 109)
  - Local 629: Bliley Electric (Box 15, Folder 110)
  - Local 630: Westinghouse, Sunbury (Box 15, Folder 111)
  - Local 633: Sylvania, Warren, PA (Box 15, Folder 112)
  - Local 634: Westinghouse, Beaver, PA (Box 15, Folder 113)
  - Local 635: Sylvania, Johnstown, PA (Box 15, Folder 114)
  - Local 636: Sylvania: Mill Hall (Box 15, Folder 115)
  - Local 639: Sylvania Electric Products, 1949-1960 (Box 15, Folder 116)
  - Local 639: Sylvania Electric Products, 1960-1976 (Box 15, Folder 117)
  - Local 641: Pittsburgh Aluminum Alloy (Box 15, Folder 118)
  - Local 642: Gibson Electric Company (Box 15, Folder 119)
  - Local 643: Norbatrol Electric Corporation (Box 15, Folder 120)
  - Local 644: Femco Incorporated (Box 15, Folder 121)
  - Local 645: Precise Metals & Plastics (Box 15, Folder 122)
  - Local 646: Crown Creative Industries (Box 15, Folder 123)
  - Local 647: Leland Corporation (Box 15, Folder 124)
  - Local 650: Custom Concept Incorporated (Box 15, Folder 125)
  - Local 651: Armstrong Fixtures (Box 15, Folder 126)
  - Local 688: St. Mary's Manufacturing (Box 15, Folder 127)
  - Local 694: Devilbiss, Somerset, PA (Box 15, Folder 128)
  - Local 699: Pennyoil (Box 15, Folder 129)
  - District 6: UE District Six Council (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - District 6: Kennywood Picnic (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - District 6, 1940s (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - District 6: A Living Nightmare for A.W. Robertson (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - District 6, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - District 6: Dayton Conference, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - District 6: UE General (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - District 6, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - District 6: Congressmen at District 6 Council, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - District 6, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - District 6, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - District 6, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - District 6, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - District 6: Twenty Year Awards, July 1963 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - District 6, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - District 6, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - District 6: Delegation to Washington D.C., 1967 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - District 6: Council Meeting, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - District 6, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - District 6, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - District 6, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - District 6: Delegation to Washington on Wage Freeze, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - District 6, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - District 6: Council Meeting, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - District 6: Energy Meeting, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - District 6, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - District 6: Council Meeting, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - District 6, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - District 6: Protest High Gas Costs, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - District 6: Council Meeting, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - District 6: Council Meeting, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - District 6: Assisting Striking Miners, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - District 6, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - District 6: Women's Conference, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - District 6, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - District 6, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - District 6, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - District 6, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - District 6, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - District 6, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - District 6, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - District 6, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - District 6, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - District 6, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - District 6: Social Life, 1940s-1950s (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - District 6: General: Children (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - District 6: General: Small Photographs and Negatives (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - District 6: General: Large Group Photographs (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - District 6: General: Small Group Photographs (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - District 6: General: Portraits (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - District 6: General: Unidentified (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Photographs to be Processed and Refiled (Box 17)
  - Local 701: Simplex Radio; Sandusky (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Local 703: Akron (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Local 705: Alliance Mfg., Alliance (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Local 706: Federal Machine and Welder, Warren (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Local 707: General Electric, Cleveland (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Local 709: Hoover, Canton (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Local 710: Apex Electrical Mfg., Mansfield (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Local 710: Apprenticeship Training Program (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Local 711: Mansfield (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Local 713: General Electric, Bellevue (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Local 714: G. and C. Foundry, Sandusky (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Local 715: Reliance Electric, Cleveland (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Local 716: Simplex Radio, Sandusky (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Local 717 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Local 718 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Local 719: Warren City Mfg., Warren (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Local 720: Westinghouse, Geneva (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Local 721 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Local 722: General Electric, Warren (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Local 723: Lincoln Molded Plastics (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Local 724: Westinghouse, Lima (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Local 730: Federal Machine and Welder, Warren (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Local 731: General Electric, Conneaut (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Local 731: General Electric, Conneaut, 1980-1990 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Local 732: GE Packard, Tiffin (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Local 734: Eighmy Corp., Conneaut (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Local 735, Cleveland (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Local 747: Ohio Brass, Barberton (Box 18, Folder 28)